want to have insurance but don't want to
deal with complicated processes, don't worry,
fwd Life Indonesia has
ifwdiberate which will make it easier for you
to get insurance services
including claim services ifw
deliberate is designed with a simple claim process
Let's look at the
following three easy steps first visit the
ifwd.co.id site and submit a claim that is
available fill in the requested data and information do
n't forget to
complete it with the required supporting documents
second send
your claim submission form along with
supporting documents via email to
cs.idfwd.com and post to the
fwd lifeones head office address that you can
find on the site third our officers
will Sega do
your documentation if needed
our officers will confirm via
Ail if your claim submission is
in accordance with the provisions then your claim process
will be completed within 7
working days we have transferred your claim funds
ifw deliberate also comes
with customer service that is
ready to help you through
chat at
1500391 every day from 8 am
to 10
pm easy isn't it so don't hesitate to
have insurance from fwd Life Indonesia
and feel how ifw deliberate
makes your life easier